Donald G. Adams Papers, Inclusive: 1962-1980, undated, Bulk: 1972-1977, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Committees, 1970-1977, undated; 3
  - Jurisprudence Committee, 1970-1973, undated; 4
    - Bills and Analyses, 63rd Legislature (2 of 3), 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bills and Analyses, 63rd Legislature (3 of 3), 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1968-1977, undated; 4
  Series IV contains the correspondence sent to and from Donald Adams during his time in the Texas House and Texas Senate. Series IV is divided into two subseries, State Representative and State Senator. Within each subseries, the materials are sorted alphabetically by topic, then chronologically where appropriate.
  Adams' constituents sent him a large amount of correspondence, much of which he answered personally. This correspondence covered a wide variety of issues, including agriculture, education, public utilities, and the Equal Rights Amendment. Beyond legislative and political issues, Adams also received requests for help with various predicaments from his constituents, including difficulties receiving social security and insurance payouts, worker's compensation, parole, military leave, etc. Finally, Adams received invitations from different organizations, some of which asked him to deliver a speech. These invitations and Adams's replies are contained in this series, sorted chronologically by month. This series is in generally good condition, with a few faded but still legible documents.
  - State Representative, 1968-1972, undated; 1
    - Agriculture, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Airports, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Budget and Revenue, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Drugs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Education, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Elections, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Employment Applications, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - General, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Health and Welfare, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Hunting, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jails, Criminal Justice, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Report, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - New Constituents, 1971, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - North Texas State University, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Office Affairs, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Parks, Community Improvements, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Prisoners of War, 1971, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Probate, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rivers, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Roads, Transportation, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Speeches on Texas Constitutional Amendments, 1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - State Employees, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Taxes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - State Senator, 1972-1977, undated; 2
    - Abortion, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture, 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Agriculture Extension Service, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Air Pollution, 1973-1976, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Airports, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Alcohol, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Alcoholism, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 1975 Appropriations Bill Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 1975 Appropriations Bill Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Austin State Hospital, Adult Education Program, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Auto Insurance, Auto Industry, and Licensing, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Banking and Loans, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Bicentennial Celebration and Preparation, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Big Thicket National Preserve, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Blindness, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Business and Industry, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Capital Punishment, Life Sentences without Parole, 1973-1977, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Carter Presidential Campaign, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Children, Childcare, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Children and Youth Commission, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, Racism, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Committees, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Cosmetology, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Daylight Savings Time, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Drugs, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Education, Adult Education, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Education, Colleges and Universities, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Education, Colleges and Universities, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Education, County School Superintendents, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Education, English Classes [Letters in Spanish], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Education, Schools, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Education, Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Education, Schools, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Education, Schools, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement, 1972-1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Elections, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fire Ants, 1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Firefighters, 1975-1976, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Football Tickets, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Forestry, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gambling, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gun Control, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Health, Health Insurance, and Health Department, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Hunting and Fishing, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Impeachment, O.P. Carillo, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Impeachment, Richard Nixon, 1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Independent Order of Odd Fellows Petition, Charity Homes, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Indian Affairs, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Judicial and Legal, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Juvenile Crime, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Labor and Employment, 1972-1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice, 1972-1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Legislation, Bills, General, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, Bills, General, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, Bills, General, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, Bills, General, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, Bills, General, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Letters from Schoolchildren, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Libraries and Archives, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Little League, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Marriage and Family, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Military, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mission Nuestra Senora Dolores de los Ais Archeological Project, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Mission Nuestra Senora Dolores de los Ais Archeological Project, Report on Investigations, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - National Federation of Independent Businesses, Surveys, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Office Affairs and Management, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Oil, Energy Crisis, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Oil, Energy Crisis, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Oil, Energy Crisis, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Oil, Energy Crisis, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Oil, Energy Crisis, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Parks, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Parks, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Parks, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Parks, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Probate, Wills, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Project “Imagine” Incorporated, Child Care, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Public Employees, 1972-1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Public Utilities, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Public Utilities, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Public Utilities, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Public Utilities, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Public Welfare Book Copies, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Railroads, 1973-1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Right to Work, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1973 January-June (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1973 July-December (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Roads and Infrastructure, Highway Department, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Roads, Loop 224, Nacogdoches, 1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Charles Schnabel Scandal, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Senior Citizens, Nursing Homes, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Soil and Water, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Soil and Water, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Soil and Water, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Soil and Water, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - State Bar, Sponsored Bills, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - State Budget and State Spending, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Sunday Closing Laws, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, General, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Taxes, Property Tax, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, Sales Tax, 1972-1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Texas Constitutional Convention, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - “Texas Forestry”, Newspaper, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - “Texas Labor”, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Newspaper, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - “The Texas Observer”, Newspaper, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Texas Rehabilitation Commission, 1975-1976, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Veterans, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Welfare, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Welfare, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Welfare, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Worker’s Compensation, Industrial Accident Board, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1972 November (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1972 December (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 January (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 February (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 March (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 April (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 May (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 June (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 July (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 August (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 October (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 November (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1973 December (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 January (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 February (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 March (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 April (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 May (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 June (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 July (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 August (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 September (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 October (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 November (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1974 December (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 January (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 February (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 March (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 April (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 May (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 June (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 July (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 August (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 September (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 October (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 November (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1975 December (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 January (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 February (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 March (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 April (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 May (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 June (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 July (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 August (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 September (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 October (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 November (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1976 December (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 January (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 February (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 March (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 April (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 May (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 June (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and Appointments, 1977 September (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Birth Announcements and Congratulations, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Birthday Notes, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Congratulations, Elections, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Congratulations, General, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Congratulations, Graduations, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Deaths and Condolence Notes, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Get Well Soon Notes, 1973-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Thank You Notes, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Thank You Notes, 1973 January-June (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Thank You Notes, 1973 July-December (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Thank You Notes, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Thank You Notes, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Thank You Notes, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Job Recommendations and Appointments, 1973 January-June (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Job Recommendations and Appointments, 1973 July-December (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Job Recommendations and Appointments, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Job Recommendations and Appointments, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Job Recommendations and Appointments, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Job Requests, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Job Requests, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Job Requests, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Job Requests, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Job Requests, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Issues, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Constituent Issues, 1973 January-June (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Issues, 1973 July-September (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Issues, 1973 October-December (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Issues, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Issues, 1975 January-June (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Issues, 1975 July-December (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Issues, 1976 January-June (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Issues, 1976 July-December (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Issues, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Legislative, 1967-1977, undated; 5
  Series V. Legislative contains copies of bills from Adams’s time in the Texas Legislature as well as correspondence and other documents related to various bills. The series is divided into five subseries, one for each session of the Texas legislature in which Adams served. Each subseries is divided between legislation introduced or cosponsored by Adams during the session and other legislation from the session. These divisions are sorted by bill numbers if they are identified and by loose topics when a specific bill is not the folder topic. Among the major legislative issues covered during Adams’s tenure are the reform of volunteer firefighters’ pension programs, the overhauling of Texas’s family and criminal justice codes, and the reconstruction of the Texas State Constitution (for which Adams served as a delegate). The series is in good condition.
  - 61st Legislature, 1967-1973, undated; 1
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Voter Opinion Questionnaires, 1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Legislative Reports and Newsletters, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Forestry, Correspondence and Print Materials, 1969, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Property Taxation, Booklets and Printed Materials, 1967-1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Called Session, Tax Legislation (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Called Session, Tax Legislation (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Called Session, Tax Legislation (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Called Session, Clippings, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Texas Constitution Amendment, Department of Public Welfare, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Texas Constitution Amendment, Texas Water Plan, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Texas Constitutional Amendments, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Sewage Disposal Bill, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Interim Committee on the Imported Fire Ant, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Interim Penal Code Study Committee, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Penal Code Revision Endorsements and Materials, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Penal Code Revisions and Drug Legislation (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Penal Code Revisions and Drug Legislation (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - SJR 15, Texas Amendment #3, Property Tax Adjustments, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HJR 31, Texas Amendment #3, Property Tax Adjustments, 1969-1970, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 69, State Assistance for Surviving Family Members of Dead Firefighters and Law Enforcement Officers, 1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Amendment to HB 810, Entering Land without Consent, 1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - HJR 4, Texas Constitution Amendment, Assistance to Surviving Spouses and Children of Governmental Employees, 1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 62nd Legislature, 1969-1972, undated; 2
    - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Interim Activities Heading into 62nd Legislature, 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions about House Speakership, 1972, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Redistricting Maps (1 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Redistricting Maps (2 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Redistricting Maps (3 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Governor’s Study Committee on Automobile Insurance Rates, 1972, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - HR 75 and HB 1333, Timber Legislation, 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Parks and Recreation Bill Analyses, 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Meat Inspection Committee (1 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Meat Inspection Committee (2 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Vendor Drug and Healthcare Programs, 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Tax Bills (1 of 2), 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Tax Bills (2 of 2), 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - HB 72 and HB 73, Insurance and Financial Bills, 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - HB 1643, Relating to the Compensation of the Criminal District Attorney of Harrison County, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - HB 1763, Qualifications and Examinations for Public Accountants, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - HJR 75 and SJR 50, Amendment #3, 1972, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - HJR 266, Sharpstown Bank Investigation, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - SB 729, Amendments, Commissioner’s Court of Jefferson County, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - SB 749, Highway Beautification, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - SB 875, Methods of Assessing Open Space Lands, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - SJR 50, Amendments, 1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Legislative Reports, 1971-1972, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Honorific and Memorial Resolutions, 1971, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Proposed Legislation, Setting Amounts for Bail, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Legislation, Requirements for Hauling Wood, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - “Texas Fireman’s News”, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Volunteer Firemen, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 326, Relating to the Use of Artificial Devices to Call Fox, 1971, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - HB 370 and SB 225, Amending and Revising Portions of the Texas Probate Code (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - HB 370 and SB 225, Amending and Revising Portions of the Texas Probate Code (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - HB 428, Repealing Previous Fish Farming Law, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - HB 429, Jurisdiction of Appeals from Awards of Eminent Domain, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - HB 501, Transfer of Persons to the Texas Department of Corrections Pending Appeal, 1970, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - HB 589, Child Support Payments Extended, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 591, Amending Labor Laws Regarding Hours, 1971, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 657, Requiring a Jury Determine Mental Competency in a Criminal Action, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 943, Relating to Appointment of Appraisers for Letters Testamentary, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Amendment to HB 1255, Pornography, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 1280, False Identification, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 1320 and SB 711, Collection of Fees for Attorney Licenses, 1971, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - HB 1324, Medical Services Recovery Act, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - HB 1404, Increasing Fees for In-Transit License Plates, 1971, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - HB 1435, Relating to Use of County Resources on Private Roads, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - HB 1536, Authorizing the Parks and Wildlife Department to Exchange Certain Sections of Palo Duro State Park, 1971, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - HB 1537 and SB 714, Establishing a Natural Rivers System, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - HCR 3, Amending Rules of the Legislature, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - HCR 11, State Official License Plates for Board of Education Members, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - HCR 14, Creating the Joint Legislative Committee on Administration, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - HJR 17, Amending Rules of the Legislature, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - HJR 57, Texas Constitution Amendment, Determining Mental Competency to Stand Trial, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)